A Guide to the Papers of James J. Kilpatrick
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - 1956-1965 Correspondence: Mi - Milio (Box-folder 35:7)
    H.A. Michaels Sr., Anthony Michalek, Michie Company, Mrs. J.T. Michie, Leroy Mickins- North Side State Farm, Micro-Photo, Microfilm, Martha H. Middleton- Birdwood Farms, Mrs. Richard H. Middleton, Claude W. Milam- Harrisonburg High School, Watt Miles- Danville Commercial Appeal, Rabbi Jacob Milgrom, E. Victor Milione- Intercollegiate Society of Individuals
  - 1959 Correspondence: Military Trip (Box-folder 35:8)
  - 1958-1959 Correspondence: Military Trip (Box-folder 33:9)
  - 1958-1959 Correspondence: Military Trip (Box-folder 36:1)
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Mill - Arthur Miller (Box-folder 36:2)
    Mrs. Lynn Millar, Major T.H. Milldebrandt- Information and Education Officer Arizona Highway Patrol, Miller & Rhoads, Arthur S. Miller- George Washington University Law Professor
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: B.M. Miller -Louis H. Miller Jr. (Box-folder 36:3)
    B.M. Miller- Miller Welding Supply Company, Bessie M. Miller- Greenway Apartments, C.P. Miller, Charles C. Miller, Edward P. Miller- American Institute of Discussion, Ernest Miller- Public Library of Cincinnati and Hamilton County, Floyd J. Miller Sr., G. Tyler Miller- Madison College, Giles E. Miller, Henry J. Miller, Herbert J. Miller- Tax Foundation Inc., Herbert S. Miller- Oregon Legislative Interim Committee on Criminal Law, Howard G. Miller- North Carolina State, J. Clifford Miller Jr.-Miller Manufacturing Company, J. Maurice Miller- Life Insurance Company of Virginia, J. Newbill Miller- Maple Springs Farm, James A. Miller, Lambert H. Miller- National Association of Manufacturers, Louis H. Miller Jr.
  - 1954-1967 Correspondence: Margy Miller-Minn (Box-folder 36:4)
    Margy Miller, Nancy Miller- Kansas City Star, R.G. Miller- Daily Oklahoma Star, Richard A. Miller, Ridgely Miller Jr., Robert Miller, Rochelle Miller- Department of Political Science at Brown University, St. Clair Miller, Thomas R. Miller- Hustings Court of the City of Richmond, W.L. Miller, Mrs. W.L. Miller, Walter Miller- Pure Water Association of America Inc., William A. Miller- New York Herald Tribune News Service, Willis D. Miller-Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia, Fred G. Millette, William Millhorn Jr., Eugene D. Millikin, J.C. Milliken, Perry Millikin, John S. Millis- American Good Government Society, Arthur L. Mills, J. DeWitt Mills, Mason Mills, Willis J. Milner Jr. -The Life Insurance Company of Virginia, Bob Milton, Frances Mims, Earl Minderman, Mrs. Helen G. Miner, Barry T. Mines, Christopher C. Miniclier- Dickinson College, E.W. Mink, Captain John Bradley Minnick, Paul Vernon Minnick- U.S. Department of Justice, FBI
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Min - Mit (Box-folder 36:5)
    G. Gilmer Minor Jr., James M. Minor Jr., W.M. Minter, Minutes- Bill Chambless at Nationwide Insurance, William J. Missett- The Suffolk News-Herald, Frances M. Missimer, Missouri Alpha Fund, Missouri Press Association, D.T. Mitchell Jr., Gerald Mitchell- Georgetown University, Jack Mitchell, James A. Mitchell, James H. Mitchell III, Lucille O'Neal Mitchell, Dr. Ralph Mitchell, W.J. Mitchell
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Marvin Coleman Mobley (Box-folder 36:6)
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Mod - Monta (Box-folder 36:7)
    George M. Modlin- University of Richmond, Richmond Memorial Hospital, Mrs. K. Moe, Carlton Page Moffatt Jr.- Richmond Federal Savings and Loan Association, Glenn A. Moffitt, Fred G. Mohler, Mrs. William P. Molette, Raymond Moley- Newsweek Magazine, Will Molineux- Williamsburg Bureau, Newport News Times-Herald, William J. Moll, Eva Molloy, Honorable Frank P. Moncure- Virginia House of Delegates, Mrs. T. Rutherford Moncure, Virginia B. Moncure, William O. Moncure, T.S. Mondy Sr., Martha Leonard Monfalcone, A.S. Mike Monroney- U.S. Senate Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Irma Monsky, Ludwell Lee Montague, Penn Montague- Miller & Rhoads, Samuel A. Montague, V. Montana
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Montg - Robert C. Moore (Box-folder 36:8)
    George S. Montgomery Jr., H.S. Montgomery Jr.- Colonial Theatre, Judge James H. Montgomery Jr.-Juvenile & Domestic Relations Court for Richmond, VA, The Montreal Star, Monument Avenue, Mrs. Gene Moody- Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, George H. Moody- Henrico County Public Schools, Mrs. Lester S. Moody, Thelma C. Moomaw, Helen C. Moon, Dow Mooney, C.B. Moore, Clarence P. Moore, E. Blackburn Moore- Virginia House of Delegates, Ellen Moore, Elizabeth Moore, Ernest E. Moore, Faye E. Moore, G. Clinton Moore, G.W. Moore, George E. Moore, Hardy Moore, J. Leonard Moore, James D. Moore, John M. Moore, M.L. Moore, Margaret Bowe Moore, Nancy Moore, R. Cosby Moore, Robert C. Moore- American Legion Post 55, Robert C. Moore-Young Sweetser Company Inc.
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Robert E. Moore-More (Box-folder 37:1)
    Robert E. Moore- Flockhart Foundry Company, Samuel J. Moore Jr., T. Justin Moore, W. Stanley Moore- The News Herald, Waldo W. Moore, Mrs. Dwight G. Moorhead, S.L. Moors, D.H. Moreau- The Hunterdon County Democrat, John R. Moreau, Fred H. Morehead, J. Earl Moreland- Randolph Macon College, Jane E. Moreland- Madison College, John R. Moremen- Court of Appeals of Kentucky, Judith Morente MD- Medical College of Virginia
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Morg - Morr (Box-folder 37:2)
    D.P. Morgan, Evelyn L. Morgan- Seaboard Air Line Railroad Company, H.S. Morgan, James Morgan, Lelia L. Morgan, Odell Morgan, Perry E. Morgan- The Norfolk Ledger- Star, Erica Morini, Ida Moriss, V. Morita, Felix Morley- American Enterprise Association, Richard D. Morphew- Citizens Council Forum, Barton W. Morris Jr., Mrs. E.W. Morris, John C. Morris, Robert G. Morris, Willie Morris- Harpers Magazine Inc., Professor Morrison, Bill Morrison, Brad Morrison- The Minneapolis Star-Tribune, Deane Morrison, Matthew Morrison, William W. Morrison- Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Emma Morriss, Anne LaVerne Morrow, Leonard Morrow
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Mors - Moy (Box-folder 37:3)
    Howard Newcomb Morse, Robert W. Morse- Department of the Navy, Wayne Morse, Mrs. Morton, C.F. Morton- Berry-Burke Company Inc., Frederick S. Morton, George B. Morton, Hugh Morton, Marion Morton, Sidney G. Morton- Juvenile and Domestic Relations Court for Richmond, VA, Sterling Morton, William Krebs Morton, Mrs. W.K. Morton, V.H. Moseley, James F. Moser Jr., Charles T. Moses- Virginia Senate, Robert Moses- New York World's Fair 1964-1965 Corporation, Walter D. Moses and Company Inc., Herbert R. Mosley, Mrs. N. Moss- Washington Star Syndicate Inc., O.B. Moss, William F. Moss, Carl Mote Jr., Homer Mothershead, Ira S. Mothner- Look Magazine, Arnold Motley- Circuit Court of Essex County, John J. Motley, Motorola, L.C. Mountcastle, John Moyler Jr.- The Life Insurance Company of Virginia, James H.S. Moynahan
  - 1951-1966 Correspondence: Mu - Mun (Box-folder 37:4)
    Norbert G. Mudd, Mrs. C. Mueller- The Washington Evening Star, L.W. Mueller- Tradition, Helen Smith Muggler- Educational Director Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, Francis J. Mulkeen, W.A. Mullan, John B. Mullaney- The Denver Post, The Cleveland News, Dr. James W. Mullen II- Experiment Inc., Michael Ann Mullen- Manhattansville College, Ralph C. Mulligan- Bituminous Coal Institute, Josephine M. Mullin- American Association of Retired Persons, Billy Mullins- Association of Production, Maintenance, Clerical and Technical Employees, Eustace Mullins, Richard D. Mullins, C. Roy Mundee- U.S. Department of Commerce, L.H. Mundin III- Sons of Confederate Veterans, Karl Mundit, Frances E. Munroe, Pat Munroe, William Munroe, Raymond M. Munsch- Miller & Rhoads, Mrs. B.B. Munsey, Lyle H. Munson, Christian Munt- Richmond Hotels Inc.
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Mur-End "M" (Box-folder 37:5)
    Mrs. Nell Stephens Murfree, Mrs. W.A. Murfree, Mr. Murphy, Carl Murphy- Afro-American Newspapers, F.J. Murphy- The McNaught Syndicate Inc., Francis Murphy, J.L. Murphy, Mrs. John Murphy, Lawrence Murphy, Lloyd D. Murphy, Mary Teresa Murphy, W. Tayloe Murphy- Tidewater Telephone Company, William P. Murphy- University of Mississippi School of Law, Arch P. Murray, Mrs. D. Murray, Hoke Murray, Hyde Murray- U.S. House of Representatives Committee on Agriculture, Jane G. Murrell, Dr. Thomas W. Murrell Jr., Dorothea Murry, Muscogee Publishing Company, Gladyce G. Muse, Paul A. Muse, Mrs. William K. Muse, William T. Muse- T.C. Williams School of Law University of Richmond, Dr. Charles A. Muses, Senator Edmund S. Muskie- U.S. Senate Committee on Government Operations, C.M. Musslewhite, Frank Myer, Mrs. A.G. Myers, Arthur Myers, Mrs. Delpha M. Myers, E. Myers, Richard Myers, Robert J. Myers
  - 1950-1967 Correspondence: N - Navy (Box-folder 37:6)
    Longines B. Naber, Mark L. Nace, Joe Nadler-Cornell Club, Fred J. Naff- The Newport News Daily Press, Judith L. Nahouse, Dr. T. Otto Nall- Christian Advocate, Eleanor Ritchie Nall, Doris C. Nash, Edwin B. Nash, Frederick H. Nash, National Academy of Economics and Political Science, National Broadcasting Company (NBC), National Civil Liberty Foundation, National Conference of Christians and Jews, National Conference of Editorial Writers, National Congress of Parents and Teachers, National Council of Jewish Women, National Economic Council, National Health Federation, National Observer, National Review, John S. Naud, Department of the Navy, Navy League of the United States
  - 1953-1967 Correspondence: Nea - Neu (Box-folder 37:7)
    Mrs. P.H. Neal, Ruth Neder, Needmor Farm, Edwin J. Neff- The Republican Newsletter, Dr. Sidney S. Negus-Medical College of Virginia, The Neighborhood Group of Motion Picture Theatres, The Neighborhood Improvement Association, James H. Neill, Carl R. Nelson, Christian H. Nelson-National Conference of Editorial Writers, Florence Nelson, Frederic Nelson - The Saturday Evening Post, H.A. Nelson, Hale Nelson, Jane H. Nelson, Joseph L. Nelson Jr., Page Nelson, Richard Nelson, Robert F. Nelson-Virginia Travel Council, Ruth N. Nelson-National Conference of Editorial Writers, William E. Nesom, Ann Nestor, Mrs. M.J. (Bettyanne P.) Nethery Jr., William Netschert, Joseph P. Nettles-University of Richmond, Network of Patriotic Letter Writers, Sen. Maurine Neuberger
  - 1957-1967 Correspondence: Dr. Robert J. Needles (Box-folder 38:1)
  - 1950-1966 Correspondence: New - Newton (Box-folder 38:2)
    New Orleans Trip, New York Herald Tribune, New York Times, Leslie W. Newberry, Merritt Newby- American Challenge, Tom Newby, Alan Newcomb-Jefferson Standard Broadcasting Company, J. Arthur Newcomb, J. Churchill Newcomb, Franklin Newcomer-Governor's Office, H.E. Newell, Mrs. R. Bruce Newell, Capt. B.R. Newman, C.F. Newman, Ernest L. Newton-Nevada Taxpayers Association, Eugene M. Newman MD, Helen Newman-United States Supreme Court Librarian, M.D. Newman-Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, Michael C. Newman-Office of the Minister for Southern Rhodesia Affairs-British Embassy, W.M. Newman, Walter S. Newman, News Leader Current Events Club, Clarence Newsome, Newsweek, Frances M. Newton, Hugh C. Newton-National Right-to-Work Committee, J.K.M. Newton-The American Society of Chartered Life Underwriters, V.M. "Red" Newton Jr.- Tampa Morning Tribune
  - 1948-1956 Correspondence: News Leader (Box-folder 38:3)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Ni - Norm (Box-folder 38:4)
    Clara Hyer Nichol, C.R. Nichols, E.M. Nichols, Mrs. Lyle W. (Jody) Nichols, William I. Nichols- This Week Magazine, Marjorie Nicholson- Reader's Digest, Mrs. W.H. Nickels, Jr., Mrs. W.W. Nicodemus, Nieman Fellowships Committee-Harvard University-Re: William P. Cheshire, Gustaf Blaine Nissen, Mable Nissen, Paul H. Nitz-Secretary of the Navy, H.E. Nix, Rep. Robert N.C. Nix - 4 th District Pennsylvania, John Nixon Jr., Richard Nixon (Subject), Dr. Gaylord B. Parkinson, C.F. Noble, G. Bernard Noble-Department of State, Gravoer D. Nobles Jr., B.S. Noel, Sally Noel, L.P. Nolan, Father Joseph T. Nolan-St. Patrick's Church, William J. Nolte Jr., Carl Norcross- House and Home, Elizabeth Copeland Norfleet, Joseph H. Norman III-Norman Motor Company, James B. Norment-County Agent-Cooperative Extension Work in Agriculture and Home Economics
  - 1949-1967 Correspondence: Dudley C. Nichols-Virginia State Penitentiary (Box-folder 38:5)
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Norr-End "N" (Box-folder 38:6)
    M.A. Norrell Sr., Robert W. Norris-Philip Morris, North American Newspaper Alliance, North Carolina Seminar, George F. North, Suzanne Northam, Mrs. O.F. Northington, Northwestern National Life Insurance Company, John A. Norton-Roanoke Public Library, Mrs. Robin L. Norton- Hue and Cry, William J. Norton, Notre Dame, Mrs. Severn M. Nottingham, Dr. H. John November, Mrs. J.D. Nowell Sr., Ronald Nowland- Virginia Farm Bureau News, Phyllis Tenney Nowlin, George T. Nuckols, Mrs. L.T. Nuckols Jr., Marvin E. Nuckols Jr. - Industrial Commission of Virginia, Randolph W. Nuckols, Francis X. Nulty-Educational Testing Service, Mrs. E.S. Nunes, G. Lloyd Nunnally-Virginia Department of Purchases and Supply, Karon Nunnally, Nursing Home, Prof. G. Warren Nutter-University of Virginia Department of Economics, Frederick Nymeyer-Libertarian Press, Donna G. Nyreen. S.T. Nystrom
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: O - Oc (Box-folder 39:1)
    F. Michael O'Brien, Joe O'Brien-Illinois Bell Telephone Company, Dr. John P. O'Brien-Internal Medicine, Kate E. O'Brien -Farmville High School-Prince Edward Academy, D.F. O'Connell, George O'Connell-Dartmouth College News Service, Daniel J. O'Connor-The American Legion Headquarters, Leo Kearney O'Drudy Jr.-Villanova University, McLain T. O'Ferrall, P. Terrence O'Grady-National Federation of Catholic College Students, Mrs. Irvan O'Hara, Mrs. Jane O'Hara, Eileen O'Leary- The Chicago Sun-Times (Secretary to Robert E. Kennedy), William B. O'Neal-University of Virginia Museum of Fine Art, James C. O'Neil, Elizabeth O'Neill, M.V. O'Neill-The Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia, Michael J. O'Neill-Whisky Distillers of Ireland, Mike O'Neill, Curtis Oakes, John B. Oakes, D.T. Oakely, Andrew L. Oberg, A. Shelby Ochs, Martin S. Ochs - The Chattanooga Times
  - 1953-1966 Correspondence: Od - Or (Box-folder 39:2)
    J.W. Oder, Mrs. H.L. Odom, Ogden City, John W. Ogden, K.D. Ogden, Prof. E.J. Oglesby-University of Virginia Department of Engineering, Dick Ohendian, Ted Ohmer, Judge William Old - Chesterfield Virginia Circuit Court, Mrs. Howard H. Oldham, Bruce Oliphant-Kings Court of Virginia, Charles P. Olivier, James W. Oliver, Dr. Clarence P. Oliver-Human Genetics Research - University of Texas, Elizabeth M. Oliver, I. Lee Oliver-York Academy, Charles P. Olivier, Warren Olney III-Administrative Office of U.S. Courts, Elis Olson, John B. Olson, M.M. Olson, Maxine Olson, Ruth Olson, Mrs. John F. Omohundro, John Ondrovich, Gen. E. Walton Opie- Staunton News Leader - State Hospital Board, The Orange Review, Rose Orente-John Wiley and Sons, Organization to Repeal Federal Income Tax, June Ornsteen, Dr. Eduardo Ortiz Jr. DDS, Alvin Orton-Associated Press
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: J.R. Orgain Jr. (Box-folder 39:3)
  - 1956-1958 Correspondence: Captain and Mrs. Robert Whaley Orrell (1 of 3) (Box-folder 39:4)
  - 1959-1962 Correspondence: Captain and Mrs. Robert Whaley Orrell (2 of 3) (Box-folder 39:5)
  - 1963-1966 Correspondence: Captain and Mrs. Robert Whaley Orrell (3 of 3) (Box-folder 39:6)
  - 1956-1963 Correspondence: Mrs. Robert E (Elizabeth H.) Osth (Box-folder 39:7)
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Os-End "O" (Box-folder 39:8)
    Mrs. George Godolphin Osborne, Mrs. Mary Winder Osbourne, John Osman, William H. Osmond, Walter B. Osterman, F. Ostrander, David W. Otey - Life Insurance Company of Virginia, Walter G. Othmer, F. Mitchell Ott, Q.A. Ottinger, J. Robert Outerbridge, C.R. Outterson - Albemarle Paper Manufacturing, Henry Allen Overstreet, Lloyd E. Overton, Alma W. Owen, Jackie Owen, Ruth Littell (Mrs. William C.) Owen-Staunton Fine Arts Association, Arthur S. Owens-Roanoke City Manager, Earl H. Owens, J.B. Owens, T.C. Owens-Union Bag - Camp Paper Corporation, Wayne Owen, William A. Owen Jr., Irvin Owings, Oxford University Press
  - 1950-1966 Correspondence: P - Pag (Box-folder 40:1)
    C.T. Pace-"Lake for Governor", Charles T. Pace, Dr. Charles T. Pace, J.T. Pace, Virginia C. Pace, Satya Sheel Pachori, Charles E. Packard-Randolph Macon College, George E. Packard, .P. Paden, Michael Padev-Foreign Editor- Arizona Republic, Sol Padlibsky- Charleston Daily Mail, P.M. Padon, Sondra Padow, A.H. Paessler-State Water Control Board, Robert W. Paige, Archer A. Page, Edgar Rives Page, Edwin L. Page, Mrs. Gordon C. Page-Mary Baldwin College, N. Olus Page, Rosewell Page Jr., Tucker Page - University of Virginia, W.R. Page
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Pai - Parker (Box-folder 40:2)
    Silas A. Pair, George H. Palm Jr., John F. Palm, Barton Palmer, Bonnie Palmer, Mrs. F.L. (Rena) Palmer, G.B. Palmer, George H. Palmer- Marine News, Howard W. Palmer-New York Press Association, John W. Palmer, R. Graham Palmer, Vera Palmer, W. Herbert Palmer, Anthony Palumbo, Anne G. Pannell-Sweet Briar College, Henry Papale, S.W. Papert Jr., Normand J. Paquette D.D.S., Parade Publications, Parents' Committee for Emergency Schooling, Alex Parker, G.H. Parker Jr., J.E. Parker - Jamestown Maritime Corporation, J.W. Parker, Jameson Parker - American Embassy-Bad Godesberg Germany, John C. Parker, Margretta Parker, Oliver R. Parker, Oscar E. Parker-Tidewater Academy, Pegge Parker-KMTV, Justice R. Hunt Parker-North Carolina Supreme Court, Hon. T. Nelson Parker-Richmond Mayor, Victor E. Parker, W.R. Parker, William S. Parker-United States Department of Commerce
  - 1950-1954 Correspondence - "Paragraphs"-Carey Williams (Box-folder 40:3)
  - 1951-1966 Correspondence: Parkins - Patterson (Box-folder 40:4)
    C.C. Parkinson, Clarence Parkinson, F.M. Parkinson, E.B. Parks Jr., Noel E. Parmentel Jr., John Parrish, Margaret Parrish, James H. Parron Sr., John Parrot, Lucy B. Parson, John M. Parsons, N.L. Parsons, M.F. Partridge, Davis Y. Paschall-Virginia Board of Education-College of William and Mary, George W. Passage- The Daily Press, Otto E. Passman, Rudolph Pate-North Carolina State College News Bureau, Paul N. Pate, John Patillo, Dale Patrick, Edward R. Patrick, Tom Patrick - Rambler Report-Coon Rapids Community School, Mrs. Nick Patronella, N.H.M. Patten, Jack Patterson- Crusade for Freedom, John M. Patterson, Mary Bray Patterson, Robert H. Patterson
  - 1957-1966 Correspondence: Robert B. Patterson-Association of Citizens' Councils (Box-folder 40:5)
  - 1950-1966 Correspondence: Patteson - Pearson (Box-folder 40:6)
    G.W. Patteson, Randall Patton-Bemidji State Teachers College, Kenneth C. Patty-Attorney General of Virginia, C.E. Paul, Felix L. Paul, G. Hurst Paul-Defiance College, Ray M. Paul, Robert R. Pauley-American Broadcasting Company, Edwin F. Pauli, Bettie L. Paulini, Burrall Paye, Boyd H. Payne, E.R. Payne, Glenn Payne, Mrs. Irving Payne, John Madison Payne, Richard W. Payne Jr.-Press Club of Virginia, Thomas G. Paynter, R.S. Peach-Upperville Colt and Horse Show, Mrs. W.C. (Jewel) Peak, Anne Pennell, Samuel Pearlstein, Marshall N. Pearman, John W. Pearsall-Richmond Area Community Chest, Robert B. Pearsall-General Features Corporation, Allen C. Pearson, Roy R. Pearson-Prince Edward School Foundation
  - 1959-1960 Correspondence - Payola (Box-folder 40:7)
  - 1946-1950 Correspondence: Payroll Taxes (Box-folder 40:8)
  - 1950-1955 Correspondence: Drew Pearson (Box-folder 40:9)
  - 1951-1967 Correspondence: Peck - Per (Box-folder 41:1)
    Helen Peck, William Peden-University of Missouri Press, C.W. Peebles, W.S. Peebles Jr., J.C. Peele M.D., Mrs. W.W. Peers, Westbrook Pegler-New England Baptist Hospital and King Features Syndicate, Neal Peirce- Congressional Quarterly, Diane Pelka, Vonda Faye Pelon, Margaret Pelow, C.S. Pelton, Joseph L. Pemberton, Patti Pemberton- National Publisher, Lewis S. Pendelton Jr., Mrs. Andrew H. Penning, Dr. D. Sergeant Pepper, Laning Pepper - Bryn Mawr College, Mrs. H. Victor (Anne R.) Percy, W.C. Perdue, Geza Perey, H. Perkins, James W. Perkins, Col. Allan C. Perkinson, Julius L. Perlt, Norbert Perret, Robert J. Perrin, Alan R. Perry, F.B. Perry, John H. Perry Jr.-Perry Publications, Martin N. Perry - Wichita Eagle, Russell Perry, Susan Perry, W.J. Perry, John Pershing-Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike Authority, Mrs. John Pershing, Mrs. C.E. Person
  - 1956-1966 Correspondence: Peterman - Pettit (Box-folder 41:2)
    Cy Peterman, Doug Peters, George Peters-Loew's Theatre, W.D. Peters, Petersburg, Norman V. Petersen, William Lois Petersen, Elmer T. Peterson- The Daily Oklahoman-Oklahoma City Times, Emil C. Peterson, F.S. Peterson, Prof. Wilbur Peterson-University of Iowa, William S. Petitclair, George S. Petley, Francis Petracek, Jacquelin Petree-Hollins College, Samuel B. Pettengill, Mr. and Mrs. Karl Peteson, R.P. Petteway, Margaret J. Pettigrew, J. Pettit, Milton C. Pettit
  - 1955-1966 Correspondence - Ph (Box-folder 41:3)
    Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association, J. Phelow, Chester F. Phelps-Virginia Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, Chief Justice M.T. Phelps-Arizona Supreme Court, "Phews in the News" - Leo Thoroughman, Philadelphia Bulletin, Ctril Philip, Jack Philip, B.P. Phillips Jr., Cabell Phillips- New York Times, Charles H. Phillips, E. Turpin Phillips, Ed P. Phillips, Harry N. Phillips Jr., Herbert S. Phillips, Kathleen Phillips, Lance Phillips, Lucas D. Phillips, Richard Phillips, W.A. Phillips, W.K. Phillips, Warren H. Phillips- The Wall Street Journal, Wayne Phillips- Rockford Register-Republic, Photography
  - 1954-1967 Correspondence: Pi - Pla (Box-folder 41:4)
    Hymen W.J. Picard, Charles L.T. Pichel OSJ-Sovereign Order of Saint John of Jerusalem, A.L. Pickens-Queen's College North Carolina, Elise Pickering-Harper and Brothers, Lt. Col. Ernest Pickering - Salvation Army, Joyce Pickering, Charles Pickett, Deets Picket, Dorothy R. Pickett, T.L. Pickle Jr., E.R. Pickut, Clifford D. Pierce, Jr., J.B. Pierce, L.F. Pierce, Sharon Pierce, Warren H. Pierce- St. Petersburg Times, William H. Pierce-Scholastic Magazines, Sam Clay Pilkington, Mrs. E.T. Pillow, G.E. Pillow, Betsey G. Pinckney-Bryn Mawr College, Constance Pinckney, Dr. M. Morris Pinckney, Dr. Morton M. Pinckne y, Thomas Pinckney, Judge David Pine-United States District Court - Washington D.C., Jack Pinkston, John E. Pipes-Richmond City Health Department, James M. Pirie, Mrs. Albert Pirkl, Amir Pishdad, Edward J. Piszek, Mrs. E.S. Pitt, Malcolm U. Pitt Jr.-The Collegiate Schools, J. Dill Pittman M.D., James M. Pittman, R. Carter Pittman, Pix Inc., Plagiarism, Allan B. Plank, City Planning Commission, Gen. Platoff Don Cossack Chorus and Dancers, Willis Player-Pan American World Airways
  - 1954-1966 Correspondence: Ple - Pol (Box-folder 41:5)
    Roger W. Pleastanton, Eugene S. Pleasonton, George R. Plumb, Plume and Sword, Mrs. Daniel C. Plummer, Richard C. Poage, Poe Foundation, P. Henry Poehler, Poetry Letters, O.A. Pohlig Jr., Mrs. Andrew J. Pohlman, Garnett R. Poindexter, Jr., Thomas L. Poindexter, Paul R. Poirot-Foundation for Economic Education, Dr. F.F. Pokorny, George W. Polhemus, Political Orthopaedic Society, Edward H. Pollaci, Jr., Theresa Pollak, Mrs. Florence H. Pollard, Fred G. Pollard, James Puller Pollard, John Garland Pollard, Ray B. Pollard, Robert N. Pollard Jr., Violet M.W. Pollard, Warren R. Pollard-Virginia Transit Company, Harry J. Polley, William Lee Polson
  - 1956-1967 Correspondence: Pon - Pov (Box-folder 41:6)